Hello everyone. With Airiko Yamano of Nyanya Konchai,
I'm Airiko Yamano from Nyanya Konchai, Kona Amano, and Nyanya Yamato from Yamato.
Today we are going to take pictures at Everyday Tamanokuni as part of our cleansing project.
Wow, it's so spacious!
And today's project at Everyday Tamanokuni is
We're going to have a showdown to see who can get the most special products!
Wow, I've always wanted to do that!
The rules are that the budget is 5,000 yen per person, and it's up to you to see how many magic tricks you can pull off.
For the small candy tricks, we'll stack 5 pieces on top of each other.
By the way, have you guys ever played the game of play?
I've been trying to get a big stuffed animal for a while now.
But they always give up and go home.
Let's try to get one today.
Do you have an Alice?
I have... five big stuffed animals.
Let's try not to lose.
What about you, Mom?
I'm not very good at this.
But Changjo's really good at it, so I watch her a lot.
I'll do my best today.
Let's get started.
I'll do my best.
Okay, I'm going to start now.
I'm going to do a big one that people don't seem to do.
I love Cinnamon.
I love Cinnamon, so if there's a stuffed animal of him
I'd like to dig it up.
Oh, this is so cute!
I want to do this!
It's so cute! Cute.
Can you do it?
I don't know how to do this kind of thing.
Well, I'll give it a try for the first time.
Wow!
Oh, but no.
Nvidia JELLY
That's great, but I feel like I can do it.
I'll keep going and going!
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, my God, this arm has so much momentum!
But it's a showdown to see how many I can get.
If it doesn't look like you can do it after a few tries, you might as well give up!
Yes!
It's a little too dense.
I'm already paying 400 yen.
The pace is a little fast.
Maybe Comer and the others are in the height group.
Oh, ahh...
Sayamocha! I'm related to Sayamocha.
Let's give it a try.
Let's do this!
Looks good!
I'm going to keep going with this one.
I hope I can hook the one that goes in front of me.
Whoa!
This could be bad.
Oh, no!
Oh! What do you think? Ah! How's it going?
Yeah!
Yay!
Yo-kan, I love Japanese sweets.
I'm waiting 100% early.
Yay! Western-style house looks delicious!
Everyone came to see the characters
You came to see the characters, didn't you?
I thought they were gone.
I was wondering where they went.
I was just in the food area.
Oh, yeah!
I'd love to have a little tea party.
Oh, great.
Here's Matsumaru. I want him.
His eyes are so cute.
I want it.
I didn't catch him. I don't know if I'll catch him.
Oh, no, Matsumaru-kun's sitting down.
Let's go again.
I don't think I can get a good shot of him.
I'll put it in.
I'm in.
He's close by.
I'm here.
Jump over.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, no, no, no.
Wait, I thought you were coming.
Wait! Yes! Wait! Yay!
Yay!
I ate it!
Bread!
Yay, yay, yay!
I got it!
I got it! I got it!
Yay!
You're not very good at this, are you?
I don't know why. I'll try to do it right.
Go for it!
Oh, that's too close!
It's so close!
It's like...
If the arm goes into the love zone...
I don't think it's a good idea
I'll be careful with that.
Oh, it's in there!
Oh, that's too close!
It's so close!
It's really, really hard.
How much have you spent already?
I think I spent about a thousand.
Are you okay?
You two seem a little...
They seem like the practical type.
I think they're going after Connor with candy.
I don't know.
Go!Go!
Whoa!
Aah! No! Let's just leave it here for once.
I'd like to go somewhere else.
Oh, man, this could be bad.
I think we might be in trouble.
What's this?
A Western-style house. I definitely want one.
I definitely want it.
Wagashi!
I'm going for the Japanese sweets!
This is a souvenir from the place of origin, so I'm curious to know what place it's from.
What do you think?
It's good.
Really? I've never done it before. My sister was a hardcore fan.
She always tells me to look to the side, but when I try it, it's difficult.
I think it's about time.
What's wrong with you?
You're moving a little slow all of a sudden. I think we should change our approach.
Do you want to give it a push? Definitely not, but I'll go for it.
Definitely not! Sorry!
Wow, you're right again!
I'm sorry for saying you're definitely wrong.
I dug it.
Oh, but just a little.
Oh!
There's something I think I can get.
Let's give it a try.
What's this?
I got it! Oh, I got it.
Are you sure about this?
Which one is it?
Well, I'm glad you got it, so I'll just keep it.
Oh, look at this.
This Cinnamon is so cute.
Can I take this one? I don't think I can.
There are so many different kinds of Cinnamon.
I can't choose one.
Please, please, please, please.
Yes, please.
Oh, no.
Mr. Sillamon fell asleep.
One more time.
Please.
Oh, no.
I'm not feeling well today.
I'll go somewhere else.
Ahh...
Oh...
Ahhh...
Ahhh...Oh, my God.
Oh!
Ahh!
Ahhh...
So cute... So cute... So heartwarming...
I found Cinnamon
Cinnamon!
Please!
No!
I'll go one more time.
I didn't know where to aim it.
I don't know.
Wait! Wait! I think it's coming!
Wait! Yes!
Yeah! I think it's coming!
Yeah!
They're here! Yay!
Yay! Finally!
I got it!
It's Cinnamon!
Yay!
Delicious!
I think you and Icoral and Mimi did a game center project.
I think you both did the Game Center project.
when Nenyasan was taking picturesWhen Nenyasan was taking pictures
When Nenya was taking pictures, she said something about not being able to take pictures if you have high expectations.
I'm sure you can't take pictures! I'm going to do it with a feeling of "I'm not going to be able to take pictures anyway!
You're not going to get it anyway!
Oh, you can't take it, can you?
Wait a minute.
I don't have any more money.
You have to spend the money carefully.
If I can't get it after spending another 300 yen or so.
I'd like to give up.
I'm begging you.
Please, please, please, please.
Please.
Oh no, I'm out of this. Retreat, retreat.
Oh, no, I don't have these, not yet.
I've been looking at food since a while ago.
I think it's time to move on.
Great.
I'd love to get some.
Oh, not at all.
Oh, but what do you think?
What? You can do this?
Really, it's amazing how good you are at UFO catchers.
Why is it so hard?
Oh, it's not so good.
I got it! I got it!
I got it, I got it, I got it!
Ta-da! Ta-da!
I'm so happy because I love racquets!
Is this tiny?
Yes, it is.
Yay!
Oh, that's not good.
I definitely want one of these.
What's with the balloon?
Oh! Oh, yeah! That's funny!
Oh! I got it! I got it!
Ta-da!
There's a Ramune on it!
It's so cute!
I love it!
I'm getting excited like a theme park visitor
I'm getting excited like a theme park visitor!
It's a little difficult.
It worked!
I could fly.
I could fight.
I did it.
I think I did pretty well for myself.
This one is cute too
My Melo.
I wonder if I can get it if I cheat.
I don't know.
I'll give it one try.
Please.
What should I do with the camera?
Is there anything you can do without a camera like this? Is there anything you can do without a camera like this?
I don't think so.
I'm pretty sure we've all had at least one shot like this.
I'm running a little low on cash.
I'd like to go to the candy shop.
I wonder if I can take a picture of a good candy bar or something.
But you have to take five of them.
So I'm thinking one stuffed animal would be better.
I don't know what to do...
This Pome-chan...
It's a different Great Pyrenees!
I'll make a decision here.
I'll go.
I'll do it.
Wow.
Oh, but you're standing up.
I'm not saying it's okay if you stand up, but...
Go ahead.
I fell asleep.
Yeah!
Go!
Oh!
Wow!
Here we go.
Yeah!
It's really hard already
Here we go
Yes!yeah! (sound made by sheep)
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
what do i do?
Nine, 10, 11, 12, 13.
Okay, I have 1,300 yen.
I'll do 300 yen.
I'll use the remaining 1,000 yen for something else.
If you get this, I'll be fine, so please, just get it.
Three, two, one.
No! I don't know what to do!
I'll give you 500 more yen.
I'm screwed! Maybe this is gambling.
Let's keep going, keep going.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is there such a thing as a zero-controller?
Is this your first test drive, Zero-Con?
Oh, man, this is bad.
Oh, no, I don't want to do that.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I can't get it, I can't get it.
I'm glad I tried.
I'll never let it go.
I'll never let go of this cigarette.
It's so cute!
Special time.
With my little buddy.
My special.
Oh, my God.
That's nice. That's good.
Oh.
Let's hear this one.
It's a little bit different.
This one's a little different, but it's really good.
Ah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
French salad looks delicious!
After all, it's important to decide whether or not to use them after you take them!
I hope it's okay.
I'd love to have it.
I'd love to have it in my heavenly home.
What do you think?
How about this one?
Yes.
Can you put it in the open space?
Yes, that's right.
But it's too thick.
We'll have to discuss it further.
Wait a minute! It's only 500 yen!
It looks so good, I'd like to use it all!
I'd like to put it in the widest space.
It's not good! It's in the back! It's too deep!
I'm going to do it this way.
Oh, that's good.
Oh, no.
I'm in a bit of trouble.
I'm so frustrated.
I'm sorry, I might not be able to do two more.
I'm going for the third crease.
This is really a little frustrating. This is really a little frustrating.
If I don't get this...
Please! Please! Please!
It's not good.
The stakes are high.
There's only one left.
I'll try the stray.
I want to.
I'll go dance-dance-dance.
Please.
Can you fall in?
Oh, man.
Nice face.
But it's not enough. It's only the first time.
Second one.
Around the middle.
I want 5 of these!
If I don't fall off...
Third one.
Here we go.
Oh, my God, it's falling.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I got six of them.
That's good.
Good.
I'm glad there was something I could take for snacks.
Before
I don't know if I can do it.
I'm down, I'm down, I'm down.
Yay!Yay!
I got two at once!
Can I get it in one go?
I don't know.
Oh!
I got two!
I just broke them all.
It's so much fun.
I don't know...
Should I use the same method as before and raise the front?
Or do we do the back like this at the end?
I'm afraid of this.
There's only one left.
I'm going to take a chance and go to the back.
You're going to guess?
I'm scared.
I'm going for the back.
Oh, wait, there's Conor.
There's Konoa.
I'm going to hide. I'm going to hide and I'm going to look.
Let's see from this side.
Very close, very close, very close, very close.
I think I'd like to see it from the pen.
Oh, my God.
That looks really good.
I'm looking at it from the side.
Very professional!
Very good!
It's amazing to think of taking a picture of such a big product.
No, it's not good. No, it's kind of a mess.
Maybe I can't.
It's not good.
Oh, my God! Oh, thank God!
Oh, thank God!
I'm filming! I'm filming!
Why are you filming at the exact moment I'm looking at it?
I'm so embarrassed.
Yay!
We finished just in time!
That's great! I just want a replay of that.
I wish you'd replay that!
That was great!
I don't think I can do it!
What?
That's not good.
Yes! Thank God!
I spent it all!
Yay!
That was great!
I'm glad I got out the back!
This is a battle of wits! The best knight is the best knight!
Now, let's open up our top-of-the-line nick-tickets!
First, a peach, please!
I'll introduce all of them!
First of all!
Chirikawa's balloons and Ramune!
Ramune is very important!
Then, the "TABEKOKO" aquarium!
This is very popular! To Miyatori! This is so popular! For Miyatori!
I like the chocolate version at the aquarium!
I love it! So cute!
I'm attracted to Rakkotsu!
Followed by some...
Wasabi almonds!
Something jumped out at me to try!
That's right!
Next is Chayokan!
You love Western-style houses!
You definitely want a Western-style house! And it's a Sayama tea house!
I can feel the Sayama tea!
Next,
There's too many! Oh, no!
What's that? A Japanese sweets set!
Japanese sweets set!
I love it!
And last but not least, potato chips!
Huge!
I was about to take it when I saw him...
I was in a hurry!
That's all! So, what are these for?
One, two, three, four, five?
One, two, three, four, five, six?
I don't know... It's so small that it seems to be zero!
So, I got five!
Thank you very much!
Well, but it's the first time,
I was a little nervous because it was my first time playing Miho Catcher...
First time? For the first time!
Well, I'm really a little embarrassed, I am!
It was difficult!
Thank you for holding it!
Is this candy not noticeable?
It's all candy!
Let's do it!
That looks good!
Okay, one!
Cute!
Mine too!
Cinnamon!
With ribbons! That's nice!
Two!
Oh! Half a fish bowl!
Ah! That's good!
I bought so much good food!
That's still 5, right?
That's great! Yeah, five! That's great!
More than I have!
And they're takoyaki flavor! I'm from Osaka!
That's for sure! There's so many!
Wow!
We've got enough for all of Miyatori!
That's amazing!
Yes!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven!
Then, two!
Wow! So many!
Wow! Wow! Whoa! Wah! Wah!
Kina!
Oh! That's so cute!
I know you have a chest of drawers and stuff!
I have a chest of drawers too!
It's so cute!
That's it! Over here!
One, two, three, four!
That's great! It really is!
Wait! How many tiny candies does it take to make one?
Five!
Isn't it 1, 2, 3, 5?
It's a tie!
Well, I'd like to go to work!
Go to work!
I'm curious!
I think you're getting 10 or something. Maybe.
You're getting double digits or one.
Okay, one!
Cute!
So cute!
He's got a great face!
And big!
Yes, indeed!
This is my second one,
I don't have a second one...
Just this one!
Oh! What? !
One!
That's good!
I'm a little embarrassed, but here she is.
All of Momoka-chan's feelings are entrusted to her.
I hugged her the moment I got it! To her!
So, this is the result!
I'm completely defeated! I am!
It looks like Connor and I got the fork, so we are tied, right?
It was a tie!
Momoka-chan has feelings for about 5 more.
So it was a tie!
You're so sweet!
It was fun!
I had 5,000 yen, but I couldn't get around at all.
I still had a lot more in my wallet.
That's all I can say!
I had a great time at the arcade!
Thank you very much!
If you liked this video! If you liked this video, please click the Good button!
Please subscribe to our channel and leave a comment!
That's all for now!
Ladies and Gentlemen! It's Yuricorder!
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!